thevacationtimes.com 2016-03-06

# Privacy Policy

**_Newsletter - What We Collect and Why_**

  * Your e-mail address ensures you receive the newsletter in a timely manner.
  * Your name is optional and tells us who personally to address - just a nice touch.
  * Although we do not want you to miss any great travel deals, you can unsubscribe to any VacationTimes.com newsletter at anytime, by sending an e-mail to [unsubscribe@vacationtimes.com](mailto:unsubscribe@vacationtimes.com). Please tell us the e-mail address you want removed.

_**Use of Customer Information  
**_

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice shall apply to all information VacationTimes.com collects or is submitted by the user on the VacationTimes.com website or which is provided by you via telephone or any other means. 

_**THE SUMMARY  
**_

We will not ask you for information that does not have a purpose and we will not require information to be disclosed that we do not deem necessary. VacationTimes.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others in ways that differ from what is disclosed in this statement. If you accessed this site through a VacationTimes.com Affiliate/Sponsor, your information may be forwarded to that Affiliate/Sponsor.

 _ **General Information - What We Collect and Why  
**_

VacationTimes.com may include information about your visit in collective or aggregated data that does not identify you specifically. For example, we may tell our advertisers or investors the number of site visitors or the most popular vacation destinations.  
Our server recognizes domain names and the pages visited. This data is gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control and improvement of our site. VacationTimes.com does not market to children nor collect personal information about children at this site.

**_Individual Information - What we Collect and Why  
_**Your name, physical address, phone and fax number are only necessary if you enter one of our competitions or promotions or contact us for information concerning one of our promotions. We do not share this personal information with outside parties except as described in this privacy policy.  
Your contact information is needed in order to notify you in the event you win the competition. We will share this information with the Travel Providers as needed to provide service to you. In some cases, paper tickets may need to be mailed to you. The more easily we can contact you, the better we can serve you.  
VacationTimes.com will use the information you provide about yourself in order to make the VacationTimes.com website as customer friendly as possible. We want to know you to better serve you, but do not want to invade your life. We may ask you for more information about your travel interests. In the future this information may be used to help VacationTimes.com make more applicable travel recommendations. However, this information will always be optional.

 _ **Surveys and Contests - What We Collect and Why  
**_

From time to time VacationTimes.com conducts voluntary customer surveys, which may ask questions about broad background information and customer preferences. This survey information is completely optional and you are under no obligation to be a part of any survey. The information VacationTimes.com collects is used to better serve our customers by helping VacationTimes.com determine our customer's travel needs and improve the satisfaction and use of this site.  
Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include demographic information including, but not limited to: age, gender, approximate household income, how you travel, how you make your reservations, and why you travel. Information submitted in contest entries may be shared with, rented to, and/or sold to selected third parties who offer related services or products that we feel might be of interest to you. By completing any registration or providing contact information via telephone or by any other means, you expressly agree and give assent to be contacted by telephone, email, postal service, or any other means for the purpose of completing any applicable travel arrangements and to be informed of additional offers that may be available. Your contact information may be required if a prize is to be awarded to survey respondents either at random or individually. This will enable us to contact you to notify you of details regarding your prize.

 _ **Cookies  
**_

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates.

 _ **Log Files  
**_

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

 _ **Affiliates  
**_

An Affiliate/Sponsor is a Web site not owned or operated by VacationTimes.com. The VacationTimes.com name may or may not appear on the Affiliate/Sponsor site.  
You may have accessed VacationTimes.com via one of our Affiliate/Sponsor sites. Please be aware that VacationTimes.com is in no way responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of the Affiliate/Sponsor and each and every website you visit that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the VacationTimes.com website.

 _ **Sharing  
**_

VacationTimes will share aggregated demographic information with our Affiliates/Sponsors and advertisers. If you access our site through one of our Affiliates/Sponsors and make travel reservations, your Email address and personal information may be forwarded to that particular Affiliate/Sponsor. If you choose to enter one of our contests or provide personal information via telephone, email, postal service, or any other means, the information submitted may be shared with, rented to , and/or sold to selected third parties who offer related services or products that we feel might be of interest to you. By providing this information, you expressly agree and give assent to be contacted by telephone, email, and/ or postal service for the purpose of completing any applicable travel arrangements and to be informed of additional offers that may be available. 

_**Links  
**_

This site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that VacationTimes.com is in no way responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our customers to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the VacationTimes.com website.

 _ **Notification of Changes  
**_

If VacationTimes.com decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes at http://www.vacationtimes/privacy.html so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. **

LEGAL NOTICES

**  
**Applicable Law**  
This site is created and controlled by VacationTimes.com in the State of Florida.  
CUSTOMER AGREES AND AFFIRMS THAT the customer shall be bound for jurisdiction and venue purposes to the laws of the State of Florida and that any claim against VacationTimes.com shall be filed in the Circuit Court of Seminole County, Florida without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws.

WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO OUR SITE AND THESE DISCLAIMERS, TERMS AND CONDITIONS AT ANY TIME.

**Legal Notice**  
VacationTimes.com  
ANY PERSON ACCESSING THE VacationTimes.com WEBSITE AGREES TO AND IS BOUND BY THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS:

**Copyright**  
All content included on this site, but not limited to, text, graphics, logos, software, are the property of VacationTimes.com or its content suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws.  The content and software of this site may be used for shopping, browsing, purchasing and booking travel reservations and related travel products.  Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, and republication of the content on this site is strictly prohibited.

**Trademarks**  
The names, logos and taglines identify any VacationTimes.com products and services are proprietary marks of VacationTimes.com.  All other trademarks and service marks are the property of their respective owners.

**USE OF THIS SITE**  
This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold or exploited for any commercial purposes that are not expressly granted by VacationTimes.com.  VacationTimes.com and its Affiliates reserve the right to refuse service and/or cancel orders in its discretion, including without limitation, if VacationTimes.com believes the customer contact violates applicable law or is harmful to the interests of VacationTimes.com or its Affiliates.

**Accuracy of Information**  
While VacationTimes.com makes all reasonable attempts to ensure the accuracy of the information neither VacationTimes.com nor its content providers can be held responsible by the customer for the accuracy of the information for the VacationTimes.com website.  
VacationTimes.com MAKES NO EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTY AS TO THE ACCURACY ON MERCHANTABILITY OF CONTENT OR PROGRAMMING AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  
VacationTimes.COM WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.  

TheVacationTimes.com and its parent corporation, OIM Corp., are not travel agencies or sellers of travel. All travel packages, accommodations, cruises, and any other travel, services, or merchandise displayed on the TheVacationTimes.com website are sold, provided by, and/or fulfilled by unaffiliated third parties. TheVacationTimes and OIM do not offer any endorsement, approval, warranty, or guarantee of these offers or of the third party providers.  

Last updated Feb 11, 2010
